<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="problem">
        <item>问题：近几年全球气温连续上升，那么今年是否依然如此呢？</item>
        <item>问题：凭借独特口感和解乏功能，咖啡成了很多人生活中不可或缺的单品，有没有便于携带的咖啡块呢？</item>
        <item>问题：你对厦门的鼓浪屿了解有多少呢？</item>
        <item>问题：在生活中，我们该如何解决金钱和欲望的平衡问题呢？</item>
        <item>问题：在我们成长过程中，我们面对最爱的东西时，我们将会如何取舍呢？</item>
        <item>问题：在学习中，我们常常提到要在玩中学习，也有游戏化学习，那么工作能游戏化吗？</item>
        <item>问题：关于就业与创业一直是社会的热点话题，在校大学生对此也比较关注，那么在校大学生该如何选择呢？</item>
        <item>问题：孤独也许是人类与生俱来的一种感觉，人为什么会有这种感觉呢？</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="english_content">
        <item>    The world is on pace to set another high temperature benchmark, with 2016 becoming the third year in a row of record heat.
NASA scientists announced Tuesday that global temperatures so far this year were much higher than in the first half of 2015.
Gavin Schmidt, director of NASA’s Goddard Institute for Space Studies, said that while the first six months of 2015 made it the hottest half-year ever recorded, “2016 really has blown that out of the water.” He said calculations showed there was a 99 percent probability that the full year would be hotter than 2015.
Schmidt said the world was now “dancing” with the temperature targets set last year in the Paris climate treaty for nations to limit climate change.
He attributed part of the rise in temperatures this year to El Niño, in which warming waters in the equatorial Pacific Ocean pump a lot of heat into the atmosphere. El Niño is now ending and water temperatures in the Pacific are dropping, which should lead in 2017 to lower but still historically high temperatures.
Average temperatures for the first six months of this year were about 1.3 degrees Celsius, or 2.3 degrees Fahrenheit, above the average in 1880, when global record-keeping began, and “quite close” to 1.5 degrees Celsius above preindustrial levels, Schmidt said in a conference call with other NASA scientists.
The warming in the first half of this year extended across all parts of the planet except for most of Antarctica, Schmidt said. Warming was especially strong in the Arctic, where it had an impact on sea ice coverage.
Walt Meier, a scientist at NASA’s Goddard Space Flight Center, said that the geographical extent of the Arctic ice so far this year was the lowest for any half-year since satellite record-keeping began in 1979, largely because warm temperatures caused melting to begin as much as two months earlier than usual.
Warming of 1.5 degrees Celsius has special significance because at the Paris climate treaty in December the world agreed to aim to limit the increase in average global temperatures to that amount above preindustrial levels.
Schmidt said that although El Niño contributed to some of the increase in temperatures from last year, almost all of the increase since the 1960s was because of human-caused emissions of carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gases.
        </item>
        <item>    San Francisco entrepreneurs Geoffrey Woo and Michael Brandt have come up with a revolutionary way for coffee lovers to get their early morning caffeine fix – chewable caffeine cubes. Each 35-calorie bite-sized ‘Go Cube’ is the equivalent of drinking roughly half a cup of coffee. So if you’re running late with no time to brew a fresh cuppa joe, just pop two cubes and you’re good to go.
Go Cubes are 100 percent vegan, made of a special blend of compounds that improve memory and alertness. With a texture similar to gum drops, each cube contains 50 mg of caffeine, 10 mg of Vitamin B6, and 100 mg of L-Theanine, an amino acid found in green tea. B6 helps aid cognitive function, while theanine helps reduce the anxiety associated with a pure caffeine buzz. They also contain about six grams of sugar per cube, and come in three different flavors – pure drip, latte, and mocha.
 Brandt and Woo used crowdfunding to raise nearly $40,000, and are now all set to release Go Cubes internationally – priced at $20.70 for six packs of four. That works out to about $1.73 per cup of coffee, which is cheaper than what you get at most coffee shops.
 According to their Indiegogo page, “The amount, concentration, and ratio of each compound in Go Cubes were significantly drawn from double-blind, peer-reviewed journal studies that statistically demonstrate the compound’s efficacy and safety.” They have used a theanine-caffeine ratio of 2:1, which “significantly improves the cognitive performance and alertness, beyond just each compound standalone.”
“Our goal with Go Cubes is to combine what people love about coffee to make a cognitive-enhancing product that’s delicious, shareable, convenient, and affordable,” they revealed. “We take pride in quality products and a brand that is both smart and down-to-earth.”
As fantastic as this sounds, you can’t really shake off the feeling that Go Cubes is just a fun way of marketing brain-enhancing drugs. But that’s the perception Brandt and Woo are trying hard to fight. They want to make nootropics – chemical supplements that make people smarter and more alert – user-friendly, so that’s why they’ve chosen to package them as candy instead of pills.
But they are quick to add that Go Cubes are not a substitute for hard work, and should be used only to enhance potential and get into a productive state of mind. “In principle, I can reach that state on my own,” Brandt said. “When I first started using nootropics, what I thought was really cool is that they can help me reliably get into that state. I can take full advantage of that time every time.”
        </item>
        <item>    Gulangyu Island is located just southwest of Xiamen City. Visitors can reach it by steamship from Xiamen City in about 5 minutes. Gulangyu Island is renowned for its delicate natural beauty，its ancient relics，and its vanes architecture. The island is on China\'s list of National Scenic Spots，one of the 35 key National Scenic Spots and also ranks at the top of the t0 most-scenic areas in Fujian Province.
During the Ming Dynasty，the island was called "Yuanshazhou Island". It got its present name from the huge reef surrounding it. When the tide comes in, the waves pound the reef and it sounds like the beating of a drum. Thus the island came to be named "Gulangyu".Gu in Chinese means "drum"，and Lang "waves".
During the later Ming Dynasty，the troops of national hero Zheng Cheng gong were stationed here. After the Opium War in 1842，13 countries including Great Britain，France，America，Germany and Japan established consulates，churches，hospitals. banks and schools here，turning the island into a common concession. In 1942，Japan occupied the island until the end of the War of Resistance against Japan
Gulangyu Island has about 20000 permanent residents，all of whom enjoy a comfortable，relaxing life. Only electric-powered vehicles are permitted on the island，so the environment is free from the noise and pollution of combustion engines, Breathing the clean air. appreciating the ever-present green trees and lovely flowers ，anyone here can feel like they are in heaven. With classical and romantic European-style architecture, the island truly deserves to be called the "Architecture Museum". It is also known as the “Cradle of Musicians" and “Island of Music" because of its reputation for music appreciation.
The Island Ring Road, which circles the island, allows you to enjoy an me sights of this small but charming island.
At the foot of Sunlight Rock stands the Memorial Hall of Zheng Cheng gong，built in honor of the hero\'s feats which include expelling the Dutch colonists and reoccupying Taiwan. Wandering up the steep rock path, visitors will see many profound inscriptions left by poets， the oldest of which dates back to over 400 years. This is the main cultural sight on the hill.
Continuing on，you will see toe preserved training grounds of Zheng Cheng gong\'s troops. Near the field is a huge rock bridging two cliffs，forming a natural entrance to a cave. This is called “Old Summer Cave"(Gu Bi shu Dong)where you can feel a pleasant cool breeze. It\'s the perfect viewing spot to appreciate the scenery of Gulangyu Island. A fantastic panorama of Xiamen City，including Nanputuo Temple. Xiamen University, Hulishan Battery, etc is within view.
        </item>
        <item>    Money can’t buy happiness, right? Well, not true. According to a recent article in The Wall Street Journal, over the past few years, new research has given us a much deeper understanding of the relationship between what we earn and how we feel. The results may seem a bit obvious: Yes, people with higher incomes are, broadly speaking, happier than those who struggle to get by. But the research also shows you have to spend strategically if you expect those bank notes to put a smile on your face. Here are some ways to better spend your money:
Buy experiences, not stuff.
 In a recently published study, Ryan Howell, associate professor of psychology at San Francisco State University in the US, found that when people don’t have much money to spare, they tend to stick to material goods. "People think that experiences are only going to provide temporary happiness," he told The Wall Street Journal in an interview. "… but they actually provide both more happiness and more lasting value."
Buy lots of little things, rather than one big thing.
No matter how much money you spend on something and how special that product is, you will get used to having it over time and it will become just another object. People adapt to having new stuff, and anything that disrupts that adaptation is likely to prolong happiness, says an Atlantic article. Buying small things can give us frequent small pleasures that are different each time they occur, as they forestall adaptation.
Buy what you like.
No keeping up with the Joneses. "There are a lot of reasons someone might buy something … but if the reason is to maximize happiness, the best thing for that person to do is purchase a life experience that is in line with their personality," Howell tells Forbes. Howell recently co-authored a study finding that when people spend money just to project a certain image, it doesn’t bring happiness.
Be sure to buy time, too.
It’s also important to consider how what you’re buying will affect how you spend your time. For example, that big house in the suburbs may seem like a good idea, but according to The Wall Street Journal, a 2004 study by researchers from University of Zurich in Switzerland found that people with longer commutes reported lower overall life satisfaction, all other things being equal.
Try giving it away. Elizabeth Dunn, associate professor of psychology at the University of British Columbia in Canada, found that in countries as diverse as Canada, South Africa and Uganda, giving away money consistently made people happier. This was even true when people were giving away even when they themselves were relatively poor.
        </item>
        <item>    Jenny was a bright-eyed, pretty five-year-old girl.
One day when she and her mother were checking out at the grocery store, Jenny saw a plastic pearl necklace priced at $2.50. How she wanted that necklace, and when she asked her mother if she would buy it for her, her mother said, “Well, it is a pretty necklace, but it costs an awful lot of money. I\'ll tell you what. I\'ll buy you the necklace, and when we get home we can make up a list of chores that you can do to pay for the necklace.
And don’t forget that for your birthday Grandma just might give you a whole dollar bill, too. Okay?” Jenny agreed, and her mother bought the pearl necklace for her.
Jenny worked on her chores very hard every day, and sure enough, her grandma gave her a brand-new dollar bill for her birthday. Soon Jenny had paid off the pearls. How Jenny loved those pearls. She wore them everywhere to kindergarten, bed and when she went out with her mother to run errands.
The only time she didn’t wear them was in the shower. Her mother had told her that they would turn her neck green!
Jenny had a very loving daddy. When Jenny went to bed, he would get up from his favorite chair every night and read Jenny her favorite story.
One night when he finished the story, he said, “Jenny, do you love me? ”
“Oh yes, Daddy, you know I love you, ” the little girl said.
“Well, then, give me your pearls. ”
“Oh! Daddy, not my pearls!” Jenny said. “But you can have Rosy, my favorite doll. Remember her? You gave her to me last year for my birthday. And you can have her tea party outfit , too. Okay? ”
“Oh no, darling, that\'s okay.” Her father brushed her cheek with a kiss. “Good night, little one. ”
A week later, her father once again asked Jenny after her story, “Do you love me? ”
“Oh yes, Daddy, you know I love you. ”
“Well, then, give me your pearls. ”
“Oh, Daddy, not my pearls! But you can have Ribbons, my toy horse. Do you remember her? She’s my favorite. Her hair is so soft, and you can play with it and braid it and everything. You can have Ribbons if you want her, Daddy,” the little girl said to her father.
“No, that\'s okay,” her father said and brushed her cheek again with a kiss. “God bless you, little one. Sweet dreams. ”
Several days later, when Jenny’s father came in to read her a story, Jenny was sitting on her bed and her lip was trembling .“ Here, Daddy, ” she said, and held out her hand. She opened it and her beloved pearl necklace was inside. She let it slip into her father’s hand.
With one hand her father held the plastic pearls and the other he pulled out of his pocket a blue velvet box. Inside of the box were real, genuine , beautiful pearls. He had had them all along. He was waiting for Jenny to give up the cheap stuff so he could give her the real thing.
        </item>
        <item>    Angry Birds, Call of Duty or online bingo? Whatever your preference, games have become part of many people’s leisure, so it was only a matter of time before someone found a way to transfer it to the world of work. “Gamification is when video games and business have a baby,” says Mario Herger, founder of consultancy Enterprise Gamification. The common definition is “using game design elements and principles in a non-game context”.
Gaining in popularity over the past few years, the point of gamification is to make mundane, difficult or time- consuming tasks more fun so we do them more effectively. It works, Mr Herger says, by tapping into our natural curiosity and sociability, desire for mastery and having fun.
Some games also use the “flow” principle, where a game’s difficulty is carefully matched to skill: initially, it is kept simple but as soon as you figure out how the game works, the difficulty notches up. Importantly, the immediate and constant feedback that online games give, whether cheering birds — as in Angry Birds — or the allocation of points, is being incorporated into the work version.
“Companies are now using systems such as BreatheHR to encourage faster feedback in appraisal systems and praise from co-workers to motivate their employees,” says Pete Jenkins, founder of consultancy Gamification+.
But gamification remains a niche tool mostly used in recruitment, learning and development, and sales.
Call centres have taken up systems such as that by Playvox, which helps companies develop gaming strategies that use leader boards, levels and performance metrics to turn a boring job into a more enjoyable competition. Seriosity has created a game to deter people from sending too many emails. Deloitte, the professional services firm, developed its own app called Who What Where, in which consultants share information about clients and projects to improve collaboration.
Games can never apply to every aspect of work. But for measurable goals, gamified personal productivity apps can be useful. Mr Jenkins uses Trello, a task management app: “I particularly like the progress bar it shows as you tick elements of a task completed.” It is also a good example of gamification not having to look like a game to be effective, he says.
Other popular apps include Habit RPG and Todoist Karma, where good habits are rewarded with points, or Task Hammer and Epic Win, which also include role play.
Although gamification has become a buzzword among HR directors, the truth is that take-up is limited. In some cases, that was because of the temptation by companies to tack on poorly designed gamification apps just to look the part. In such cases, games fail because the incentives they offer workers are meaningless, their goals are too ambitious or they are becoming boring and a distraction.
After all, most of us realise we are not in the office to have fun but to get on with our real work with real financial incentives.
        </item>
        <item>    It\'s little more than a decade since Mark Zuckerberg dropped out of Harvard at the age of 19 to launch Facebook. The social network has made him the fourth-richest man in America and a hero to any aspiring college entrepreneur.
Of course Zuckerberg was already something of a prodigy when he started his global empire. But for those with more modest abilities, there are now thousands of schools across the country offering courses in entrepreneurship.
The days seem long gone when students sought skills that would secure them a job for life working for somebody else.
"There\'s been a massive shift," says Derrick Maggard, director of the Apex Systems Center for Innovation and Entrepreneurship at Virginia Tech. "Most of these students grew up during the great recession and saw their parents, maybe their grandparents or an aunt or uncle struggle and get laid off by large companies. They\'re almost fearful to go into the corporate world. They say, I don\'t want that to happen to me - I want to do my own thing and control my destiny."
He says the most important characteristics for a successful entrepreneur are the ability to handle ambiguity and the skills to bring an idea to fruition.
Mark Zuckerberg is now worth more than $52bn, adding $18bn to his fortune in the last year alone according to Forbes. And while he represents a tiny percentage of entrepreneurs, many other successful companies have been started in a college dorm room.
Dyn was co-founded in 2001 by Jeremy Hitchcock, studying at Worcester Polytechnic Institute, Massachusetts. He developed a way to optimise the flow of data between online companies and their users to improve internet performance. Dyn, based in Manchester, New Hampshire, now employs 400 people and boasts clients such as Twitter and Etsy.
"I\'d give the same advice to any university student," says Hitchcock. "Go start a company or be part of something where you\'re creating or building, because you\'re at a time in life when you have that freedom of exploration. And do something that\'s crazy, that\'s non-traditional."
"If you are a student entrepreneur and you have an idea with a time limit on getting it to market, I would encourage you to take a leave of absence and give it a go. But those are rare," Maggard says. "Work on it while you\'re in school. Develop the idea and continue to do customer research. Then when the time is right and you are ready to move forward, go for it."
29-year-old Mehr Pastakia already had a degree in horticulture but started her rooftop garden company while studying at Johns Hopkins Carey Business School, Baltimore.
"I just wanted to learn what everybody else seemed to know about business," she says. "I had a few really great classes and really great classmates that made it totally worth it for me."
One of the most important lessons was how to manage conflict and develop self-knowledge as a leader, she says. She was also able to meet a potential investor who focuses on backing women-owned companies.
"Female entrepreneurs are on the rise," says Maggard. "But one challenge they do face is equal access to capital. Venture capitalists are known to invest less in female led start-ups."
"Research shows that women are more risk averse than men, and this can be paraded around as unfavourable," says Kathy Korman Frey, entrepreneur in residence at George Washington University and founder of Hot Mommas Project, the world\'s largest online library of female entrepreneur case studies.
But, she says, attitudes towards women entrepreneurs are changing. "If I know my investment is safer with a person who is going to consider all the options and then make a move, that\'s a (good) investment strategy."
        </item>
        <item>    Nobody likes feeling lonely, and some recent research suggests that the ache of isolation isn\'t only a psychological problem; unwanted solitude impacts physical health, too. Loneliness increases a person\'s risk of mortality by 26 percent, an effect comparable to the health risks posed by obesity, according to a study published this spring.
And because of this new evidence of the serious ramifications of loneliness, some researchers are investigating what it is, exactly, that makes lonely people stay lonely. In particular, could some behavior be at the root of their isolation?
In a paper recently published in the journal Personality and Social Psychology Bulletin, Franklin &amp; Marshall College professor Megan L. Knowles led four experiments that demonstrated lonely people\'s tendency to choke when under social pressure. In one, Knowles and her team tested the social skills of 86 undergraduates, showing them 24 faces on a computer screen and asking them to name the basic human emotion each face was displaying: anger, fear, happiness, or sadness. She told some of the students that she was testing their social skills, and that people who failed at this task tended to have difficulty forming and maintaining friendships. But she framed the test differently for the rest of them, describing it as a this-is-all-theoretical kind of exercise.
Before they started any of that, though, all the students completed surveys that measured how lonely they were. In the end, the lonelier students did worse than the non-lonely students on the emotion-reading task — but only when they were told they were being tested on their social skills. When the lonely were told they were just taking a general knowledge test, they performed better than the non-lonely. Previous research echoes these new results: Past studies have suggested, for example, that the lonelier people are better at accurately reading facial expressions and decoding tone of voice. As the theory goes, lonely people may be paying closer attention to emotional cues precisely because of their ache to belong somewhere and form interpersonal connections, which results in technically superior social skills.
But like a baseball pitcher with a mean case of the yips or a nervous test-taker sitting down for an exam, being hyper focused on not screwing up can lead to over-thinking and second-guessing, which, of course, can end up causing the very screw up the person was so bent on avoiding. It\'s largely a matter of reducing that performance anxiety, in other words, and Knowles and her colleagues did manage to find one way to do this for their lonely study participants, though, admittedly, it is maybe not exactly applicable outside of a lab. The researchers gave their volunteers an energy-drink-like beverage and told them that any jitters they felt were owing to the caffeine they’d just consumed. (In actuality, the beverage contained no caffeine, but no matter — the study participants believed that it did.) They then did the emotion-reading test, just like in the first experiment. Compared to scores from that first experiment, there was no discernible difference in scores for the non-lonely, but the researchers did see improvement among the lonely participants — even when the task had been framed as a social-skills test.
It may be difficult to trick yourself into believing your nerves are from caffeine and not the fact that you really, really, really want to make a good impression in some social setting, but there are other ways to change your own thinking about anxiety. One of my recent favorites is from Harvard Business School\'s Alison Wood Brooks, who found that when she had people reframe their nerves as excitement, they subsequently performed better on some mildly terrifying task, like singing in public. At the very least, this current research presents a fairly new way to think about lonely people. It\'s not that they need to brush up on the basics of social skills — that they\'ve likely already got down. Instead, lonely people may need to focus more on getting out of their own heads, so they can actually use the skills they\'ve got to form friendships and begin to find a way out of their isolation.
        </item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="dl_content">
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
            He <font color="#ff0000">attributed</font> part of the rise in temperatures this year to El Niño,
            in which warming waters in the <font color="#ff0000">equatorial</font> Pacific Ocean pump a lot of heat into the atmosphere.
           <u> El Niño is now ending and water temperatures in the Pacific are dropping,
            which should lead in 2017 to lower but still historically high temperatures.</u>
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
           <u>As fantastic as this sounds, you can’t really <font color="#ff0000">shake off</font> the feeling that Go Cubes is just a fun way of marketing brain-enhancing drugs.</u>
            But that’s the perception Brandt and Woo are trying hard to fight. They want to make <font color="#ff0000">nootropics</font> – chemical <font color="#ff0000">supplements</font> that
            make people smarter and more alert – user-friendly, so that’s why they’ve chosen to package them as candy instead of pills.
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
               During the Ming Dynasty，the island was called "Yuanshazhou Island". <u>It got its present name from the huge <font color="#ff0000">reef</font> surrounding it.</u>
                When the tide comes in, the waves pound the reef and it sounds like the beating of a <font color="#ff0000">drum</font>.
                Thus the island came to be named "Gulangyu".Gu in Chinese means "drum"，and Lang "waves".
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
                No matter how much money you spend on something and how special that product is,
                you will get used to having it over time and it will become just another object. People adapt to having new stuff,
                and anything that <font color="#ff0000">disrupts</font> that adaptation is likely to prolong happiness,
                says an Atlantic article. <u>Buying small things can give us frequent small pleasures that are different each time they occur, as they <font color="#ff0000">forestall</font> adaptation.</u>
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
                With one hand her father held the plastic <font color="#ff0000">pearls</font> and the other he pulled out of his pocket a blue <font color="#ff0000">velvet</font> box.
                 Inside of the box were real, genuine , beautiful pearls.
                 He had had them all along. <u>He was waiting for Jenny to give up the cheap stuff so he could give her the real thing.</u>
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
                Although <font color="#ff0000">gamification</font> has become a <font color="#ff0000">buzzword</font> among HR directors, the truth is that take-up is limited. <u>In some cases,
                that was because of the temptation by companies to tack on poorly designed gamification apps just to look the part</u>.
                In such cases, games fail because the <font color="#ff0000">incentives</font> they offer workers are meaningless,
                their goals are too ambitious or they are becoming boring and a distraction.
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
                "There\'s been a massive shift," says Derrick Maggard,
                 director of the Apex Systems Center for <font color="#ff0000">Innovation</font> and <font color="#ff0000">Entrepreneurship</font> at Virginia Tech.
                "Most of these students grew up during the great recession and saw their parents,
                maybe their grandparents or an aunt or uncle struggle and get laid off by large companies.
                 They\'re almost fearful to go into the <font color="#ff0000">corporate</font> world.
                  <u>They say, I don\'t want that to happen to me - I want to do my own thing and control my destiny."</u>
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
        <item>  <Data>
            <![CDATA[
                It may be difficult to <font color="#ff0000">trick</font> yourself into believing your nerves are from caffeine and not the fact that you really,
                really, really want to make a good impression in some social setting,
                 but there are other ways to change your own thinking about anxiety.
                 One of my recent favorites is from Harvard Business School\'s Alison Wood Brooks,
                  who found that when she had people reframe their nerves as excitement,
                  they <font color="#ff0000">subsequently</font> performed better on some mildly terrifying task, like singing in public.
                   At the very least, this current research presents a fairly new way to think about lonely people.
                    It\'s not that they need to brush up on the basics of social skills — that they\'ve likely already got down.
                    <u>Instead,lonely people may need to focus more on getting out of their own heads,
                    so they can actually use the skills they\'ve got to form friendships and begin to find a way out of their isolation.</u>
            ]]>
            </Data>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ci_hui">
        <item>
            1. attribute ：n. 属性；特质\n
                        vt. 归属；把…归于\n
                        例句：So you have text nodes, element nodes, and attribute nodes.\n
            2.  equatorial ：adj. 赤道的，近赤道的；中纬线的\n
                n. 赤道仪\n
                短语：equatorial plane  赤道平面\n
        </item>
        <item>
            1. shake off ：摆脱；抖落\n
                            例句：His companionship made it possible for me to shake off my shrinking sensitiveness.\n
            2.  nootropics ：n. 益智药；亲精神性\n
                             短语：Nootropics  Neurotonics 神经营养剂\n
            3.  supplement ：vt. 增补，补充\n
                             n. 增补，补充；补充物；增刊，副刊\n
                             例句： I use cloth napkins and cleaning cloths entirely, and I supplement with paper.\n
        </item>
        <item>
             1.reef	：n. 暗礁；[地质] 矿脉；收帆\n
                        vt. 收帆；缩帆\n
                        vi. 缩帆；收帆\n
                        短语：great barrier reef 大堡礁\n
             2.drum ：vt. 击鼓；大力争取\n
                        vi. 击鼓；大力争取\n
                        n. 鼓；鼓声\n
                         例句：The war drum is beating.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            1.  disrupt： vt. 破坏；使瓦解；使分裂；使中断；使陷于混乱\n
                          adj. 分裂的，中断的；分散的\n
                          短语：disrupt market  扰乱市场\n
            2.  forestall：vt. 先发制人，预先阻止；垄断，屯积；领先；占先一步\n
                          短语：Without Forestall  没有垄断\n

        </item>
        <item>
             1.pearl：n. 珍珠；珍珠色；杰出者；珍品\n
                      adj. 镶珍珠的；珍珠状的\n
                      vt. 使成珠状；用珍珠装饰；使呈珍珠色\n
                      短语：Pearl Jam珍珠果酱\n
             2.  velvet：n. 天鹅绒，丝绒；天鹅绒似的东西\n
                      adj. 天鹅绒的\n
                      例句：This material feels like velvet.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            1.  gamification：n. 游戏化\n
                              短语：Gamification Design  游戏化设计\n
            2.  buzzword：n. 流行词\n
                              短语：buzzword jargon  专门术语\n
            3.  incentive：n. 动机；刺激\n
                            adj. 激励的；刺激的\n
                            例句：If they have a direct incentive to do so they will think about it.\n

        </item>
        <item>
            1.Innovation：n. 创新，革新；新方法\n
                            短语：Technology Innovation  技术创新 ; 科技创新 ; \n
            2.  Entrepreneurship：n. 企业家精神\n
                         短语：entrepreneurship education  创业教育 \n
            3.corporate：adj. 法人的；共同的，全体的；社团的；公司的；企业的\n
                         例句：herefore, Business and IT should form a corporate strategy together.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            1.  trick：n. 诡计；恶作剧；窍门；花招；骗局；欺诈 \n
                       vt. 欺骗；哄骗；装饰；打扮\n
                       adj. 特技的；欺诈的；有决窍的\n
                       例句：Your trick won\'t be slipped over me.\n
            2.  subsequently：adv. 随后，其后；后来\n
                       短语：subsequently to  在…之后，继…之后\n

        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="fan_yi">
        <item>
            这种现象现在正在结束，太平洋的水温正在下降。在此作用下，2017年的气温应该会有所下降，但从历史角度来看依然属于高温。
        </item>
        <item>
            虽然听起来很棒，但或许你还是觉得“来一块”不过是用巧妙的方式推销一种提神醒脑的药物罢了——换汤不换药。
        </item>
        <item>
            因周围巨大的海礁受到海浪的阵阵冲击，发出犹如擂鼓的声音，故后改名为“鼓浪”屿。
        </item>
        <item>
            买一些小物件则能在上一件物品失去新意之前，不断带给我们新的愉悦感。
        </item>
        <item>
            他一直在等着珍妮放弃她那串廉价项链，好送给她真正的珍珠项链。
        </item>
        <item>
            在某些情况下，原因在于企业容易仅仅为了显示自己跟上了潮流而采用设计得不好的游戏化应用。
        </item>
        <item>
            他们说不想类似的事情发生在自己身上-他们想做自己的事情，掌握自己的命运。
        </item>
        <item>
            他们需要的是努力不让自己胡思乱想，这样他们就可以真正地用上自己已经拥有的社交技巧去建立友谊、走出孤独
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mymj_content">
        <item>
            Readers are plentiful. Thinkers are rare.$阅读的人很多，但思考的人很少。
        </item>
        <item>
            You must continue to dream the wild dream that you dreamed when you were young.$你必须不停地追逐年轻时的疯狂梦想。
        </item>
        <item>
            It\'s not the hours you put in your work that counts, it\'s the work you put in the hours.$工作效益不在于时间长短，而在于真正做了什么。
        </item>
        <item>
            Truly, would you not for less than that make the tour around the world? $讲真，难道人们真的不可能用更短的时间来环游地球一周吗？
        </item>
        <item>
            Books are the stepping stones to human progress.$书籍是人类进步的阶梯。
        </item>
        <item>
            Much effort, much prosperity.$越努力，越幸运。
        </item>
        <item>
            You aspire to do great things? Begin with little ones.$想成就大事，就要从小事开始。
        </item>
        <item>
            The only limits in our life are those we impose on ourselves.$生活中的唯一限制是我们加诸在自己身上的。
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>